New York State Department of Labor Files 6152
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Department of Labor Files
1950-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Department of Labor
6152
89.5 cubic feet
83.5 linear ft.
Records.
5821404
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 25, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining -- New York (State); Industrial relations -- New York (State); Arbitration, Industrial -- New York (State); Unemployment insurance -- New York (State); Workers' compensation -- New York (State); New York (State). Department of Labor-- Archives
5821404
- NYS Dept. Labor (Box 1, Folder 1)
- GF: Biography File Beinstock, Herbert (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Unemployment Insurance: Purposes and Principles (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bureau of Labor Welfare (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Paper box Strike - Memorandum (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Development and Functions of NYS Dept. Labor (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Mandatory order no. 1 governing minimum wages in the laundry occupations (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Mandatory order No. 1 - Minimum Wages (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Memo on Dept. Reorganization (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Div of Research, Statistics Publications (Box 1, Folder 10)
- NYS Dept Labor (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Protection of Migrant Workers (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Memo To: Trade Unions (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Organization Charts (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Organization Charts (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Industrialization (Box 1, Folder 16)
- What the Div of Statistics Does (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Publications preceding enactment of Unemployment Insurance Law (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Fifty Years of Employment and Earnings (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Labor (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Ten good Reasons to Hire the Handicapped (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Chapter 793, law 1944 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Order No. 2 Prohibiting Industrial HW (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Order No 3 Prohibiting Industrial HW (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Suspension of HW order No. 3 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- NYS Equal Pay Law (Box 1, Folder 26)
- NYS Equal Pay Law (Box 1, Folder 27)
- General Order Restricting HW (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Info for Employees (Box 1, Folder 29)
- News Releases on Orders Restricting Industrial HW (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Order No. 5 governing HW on Typing, addressing, mailing, etc. (Box 1, Folder 31)
- HW Order No. 4 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Hearing on HW (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Child Labor in HW Industries (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Brief History of HW (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Packet of Material on HW (Box 1, Folder 36)
- The Effect of a Korean Truce on our Economy (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Factory Exit provision held Constitutional (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Defining Extraordinary Emergency (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Reviewing Section 8-A of the Labor Law (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Elmer F Andrews Report (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Bernard L Shientag (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Labor Law in Canneries 1914 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Summary of a Brief Prepared by the Joint Legislative Conference (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Memo on the 48 hour Work Week (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Interim Report (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Regarding Application of Section 508 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- State of NY Dept of Labor (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Info on Wages etc. (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Article 5 on Labor Law (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Supreme Court Special Term (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Court of Appeals State of New York (Box 1, Folder 52)
- W. H. H. Chamberlain Inc. (Box 1, Folder 53)
- The People of the State of New York, Respondent against Elite Steam Laundry, Inc. Defendant Appellant (Box 1, Folder 54)
- People of the State of New York vs. Elite Steam Laundry, Inc. Applt. (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Directory of Labor Organizations in New York State (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Info for Health Officers Concerning Issuance of children's Employment Certificates (Box 1, Folder 57)
- War Emergency Act, Article VIII Administrative Procedure (Box 1, Folder 58)
- NYS Department of Labor Grants to States Program and Budget Plan FY 1977 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Materials Relating to Migratory Farm Labor in New York State (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Workers' Health Hazards - Today and Tomorrow Silicosis and Other Occupational Diseases (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Legal Regulations of Children Employment in Agriculture (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Public Employment Exchanges (Box 1, Folder 63)
- The Industrial Board (Box 1, Folder 64)
- moved (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Manpower Policy in NYS (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Record on Appeal NYS SC (Box 1, Folder 67)
- NYS Minimum Wage Orders and Their Effective Dates (Box 1, Folder 68)
- NYS statutory Minimum Wage Law (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Memo to Commissioner Catherwood Commissioner Dun Mr. Green From Abe Lavine C A Pearce (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Refugee Relief Act of 1953 Information Bulletin No. 4 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Order No. 1 Prohibiting Industrial HW in the Mens' and Boys' outer Clothing Industry (Box 1, Folder 72)
- General Order restricting HW (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Mandatory order No. 2 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- NYS Bulletion Labor (Box 1, Folder 75)
- NYS Labor Bulletin No. 6-a (Box 1, Folder 76)
- NYS Labor Bulletin 5-a (Box 1, Folder 77)
- NYS Labor Bulletin 4-a (Box 1, Folder 78)
- NYS Labor Bulletin 3-a (Box 1, Folder 79)
- NYS Labor Bulletin 2-a (Box 1, Folder 80)
- NYS Labor Bulletin 1-a (Box 1, Folder 81)
- State laws regulating hours and wages (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Labor Laws in NYS Minimum Wage For release 1931 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- For Realize 1931 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- The State of Golf Caddies (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Memo for Correspondence of Course (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Explanation of Min Wage Bill (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Passage (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Summary of Work Conditions in Power Laundry Industry (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Development of Labor Law in New York (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Child Labor on Farms (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Survey of Employment Agencies (Meeting March 30, 1967) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Industrial Council Committee on Wage July 7, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- The Little Falls Texture Workers Dispute (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Working Conditions in New York City Steam Laundries (Box 2, Folder 6)
- State of New York, Department of Labor (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Recommendations on Minimum Wage Legislation Report, January, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Women Workers as Union Members Introduction (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Age and Marital Status of Women in New York State (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Health Insurance Plan State of New York (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Basic Minimum Hourly Rates from 1930s to 1960s (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Opinion of NYS Court of Appeals: Mary Lincoln Candies vs NYS (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Min Wages and Max Hours for Beauty Shop Workers (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Hours of Females over 18 in the grape packing industry (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Min Wages in Beauty Shop Occupations Feb, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Wages in the Restaurant Industry Article 19 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Min Wages in Confectionary Industry (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Min Wages in Laundry Occupations (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Beauty Service Occupations in NYS Article 19 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Message to the Governor (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Mater of Gold Caddies being Considered Employees of a Golf Club (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Hand Laundry Industry - Industrial Commissioner Andrews (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Caddies, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- The People of NYS vs Diana Beck (Box 2, Folder 25)
- People of NYS vs Syracuse Home Family Laundry (Box 2, Folder 26)
- People of NYS vs Harold Siegel (Box 2, Folder 27)
- People vs Bess Morgan (Box 2, Folder 28)
- On-The-Job Training Programs (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Directory Order No. 6 Gov Minimum Wage Statements in the Hotel Industry (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Buffalo - Niagara Falls - Lockport (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Minimum Wages by Industry (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Retirement Under Industry-Wide Pension Programs Established Through Collective Bargaining (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Seasonal Farm Labor Conference July 9, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Nature and Sources of Info for Apprentices and Learners (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Report on Employment and Unemployment Conditions in the State of New York (Box 2, Folder 36)
- NYS Migrant Care Program (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Proposed Minimum Wage Orders for the Cleaning and Dyeing Industry, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Mandatory Order No. 6-c Hotel Industry (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Min Wages in Cleaning and Dyeing (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Min Wage in Amusement and Recreation Industry (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Min Wage in Cleaning and Dyeing (Box 2, Folder 42)
- State Defense Coordinator on Defense Activities (Box 2, Folder 43)
- State War Coordinator on Ware Activities of NYS dept. of Labor (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Act Vesting Authority in Industrial Commissioner (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Idle Insurance for All by NY Leader Article Aug 18, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Assoc of Commerce Bulletin, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Suffolk county and NYS DOL (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Vocational Education Program (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Bureau of Employment Security US DOL and Administrative Management Bureau NYS Division of Budget (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Report of Millinery Stabilization Commission (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Laws - Labor, Factories, and Mercantile Establishments (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Min Wage Act Article 19, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Min Wage Rates and Allowances, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage Order for Laundry Cleaning and Dyeing, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Min Wage Act for Beauty Service Industry, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Min Wage Order 3-c Confectionery Industry (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 4-d Cleaning and Dyeing Industries (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Min Wage Restaurant Industry 137 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Min Wage Hotel Industry 138 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Min Wage Retail and Wholesale 139 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Min Wage Order for Amusement and Recreation Industry effective October 6, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Building Service Industry (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Min Wage for Counselor Staff (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Misc. Industries and Occupations (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Regulations of the Industrial Commissioner (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Non-profitmaking institutions (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Min Wage Farm Workers (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Min Wage Requirements applicable to School Districts and Boards of Cooperative Educational Services (Box 3, Folder 18)
- The Brooklyn Office of the New York State Bureau of Employment (Box 3, Folder 19)
- NYS Employment Services An Analysis (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Fed Dept of Public Welfare (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Report on Unemployment Insurance Coverage in Ohio, Minnesota, and Wisconsin Submitted to the NYS Joint Legislative Comm. On Unemployment Insurance (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Outline of a Program to Revise our Unemployment Insurance System in Conformity with the Best Standards of Legislation in this Field (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Report of the Interstate Commission on Unemployment Insurance Appointed by the Governors of Connecticut, Massachusetts, NJ, NY, Ohio, Penn, and RI (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Interstate Conference on Unemployment Compensation (Box 3, Folder 25)
- The Combined Functions of Placement and Unemployment Insurance (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Special Procedures for Treatment of Union and Occupational Groups Under Unemployment Insurance (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Coverage Unemployment Insurance (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Summary of Papers Presented at New York City Conferences on Unemployment Insurance (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Unemployment Benefit Plans In the United States (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Reasons back of the Provisions of the Unemployment Insurance Law State of New York (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Unemployment Insurance Conference May 14, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Unemployment Insurance Conference May 21, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Resume of New York's Unemployment Insurance Law - With Suggested and Required Forms to be Filled Out By Employers (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Relation Between The Unemployment Insurance Provisions of the Federal Social Security Act and the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law (Box 3, Folder 35)
- General Recommendations of Metropolitan Managers' Committee of Unemployment Insurance (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Board of Inquiry on Longshore Industry Work Stoppage October-November, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Prelimnary Report of the Women's Commission to the Industrial Commissioner (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Industrial Council of the New York State Department of Labor (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Interim Report of the Committee on Labor Market Information May 15, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Governor's Conference on the Improvement of Occupational Safety Jan 10, 11, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- New York State Occupational Information Coordinating Committee (NY SOICC) (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Factual Background Summary of Night Work Laws for Women in NYS (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Preliminary Outline of Points for Discussion (Box 3, Folder 44)
- The Reporter newsletter, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Majority and Minority of the Joint Legislative Committee to Investigate the Administration of the Unemployment Insurance Law (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Partial Unemployment (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Actuarial Study of Partial Unemployment (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Second Report on Partial Unemployment, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- NYS Conference on Unemployment Insurance (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Subcommittee on the Committee of Seasonality (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Report of the Advisory Council on Minimum Wage Standards for Farm Workers, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Rochester Transit Work Stoppage May, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Report of the State Interdepartmental Committee on Migrant Camps? Jan 1, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Preliminary Report of Factory Investigating Commission Vol. I, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Preliminary Report of Factory Investigating Commission Vol. II, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Preliminary Report of Factory Investigating Commission Vol. III, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Second Report of Factory Investigating Commission Vol. I (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Second Report of Factory Investigating Commission Vol. IV (Box 4, Folder 5)
- New York State Labor Law Up to Feb 25 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Second Report of Factory Investigating Commission Vol. III, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Third Report of Factory Investigating Commission, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Fourth Report of Factory Investigating Commission vol. I, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Fourth Report of Factory Investigating Commission Vol. II (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Fourth Report of Factory Investigating Commission Vol. III (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Fourth Report of Factory Investigating Commission vol. V (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Unemployment Insurance 1940s (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1920-1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1950-1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Unemployment Insurance 1970s (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Labor Standards, Disqualification (Box 6, Folder 5)
- dis[pensation, Appropriation (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Min Wage, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 11-0026- State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance Department of Labor Docs., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- 11-0027- Advisory Council Recommendations, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- 11-0028- Advisory Council: Purpose, Function and Guidelines, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- 11-0029- State Advisory Council: Rules of Procedure, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- 11-0030- Review of Activities of the State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- 11-0031- Docs. Related to Advisory Council and Newspaper Articles, 1938-1941 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- 11-0032 Manpower Services/ Employment Service, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- 11-0033- Suffolk County, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- 11-0034 Research & Stats, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- 11-0035- Quality Control Audit Teams, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- 11-0036- Docs. Related to New York State Senate, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- 11-0037- State Advisory Council Meeting Minutes of the Committee on Financing, 1955-1963 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- 11-0038 Master Copies Nov./ Dec. 1996 list- copies made, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- 11-0039 Ann Barnes, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- 11-0040 Haldane (ET AL), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- 11-0041 Public Works Program (Doss - Employable Home Relief Recips), 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- 11-0042 Docs. Related to Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance Office of Executive Director, 1949-1959 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- 11-0043 Admin. - Pers. General - no. 1 (1936-1939) (Box 7, Folder 18)
- 11-0044 Admin. - Pers. General - no. 2 (1940-47), 1940-1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- 11-0045 Summary of Skills Program + Examples of Training Proposals, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- 11-0046- Notes, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- 11-0047- Various Reports, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- 11-0048 Division of Placement and Unemployment Insurance Personnel Statistical Report and Titles in the Division with More than 50 Employees and Status of Lists of Such Titles, 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- 11-0049- Docs. Related to Finances, 1962-1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- 11-0050- Financing Unemployment Insurance (Box 7, Folder 25)
- 11-0051 Docs. Related to New York State Department of Labor, 1951-1959 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- 11-0052 Docs. Related to New York State Labor Department and NY Times, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- 11-0053- Docs. Related to State Employment and Unemployment Advisory Council, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- 11-0054- Docs. Related to State Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Board and Referee's Cases-1951 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Board and Referee's Cases (51,62), 1951-1962 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- NYS Dept. of Labor: Liters and Reports (Misc.) 1940,1950,1964, 1940-1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Summary of a Study of a Long Term Unemployed and an Assessment of Community Resources, Problems and Needs in 12 Selected Areas of Brooklyn, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Board Cases-1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Bard Cases- 1953-54, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Board Cases-1955 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Entitlement to Unemployment Insurance Benefits: A Report Prepared for the NYS Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- NYS Supreme Court Appellate Division, Appeal Board Case No. 33,486-52 to 33,494-52 - 1954 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Court of Appeals Cases - 1955 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Court Cases - 1952 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- NYS Court of Appeals Case - Edward Corsi - 1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- NYS Supreme Court Record on Appeal - 1953 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Court - Gordon D. Sprague - 1957 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- NYS Appeals Courts (Dept. of Labor, Supreme Court) cases - 1954-1962 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- NYS Dept. of Labor and Supreme Court Appeals Cases - 1952-1954 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- NYS Dept. of Labor and Supreme Court Appeals Court Cases - 1957-1962 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- NYS Dept. of Labor and Supreme Court Appeals Court Cases - 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Letters with Industrial Relations Offices Nationwide, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Court Case 61,271-57 and Related Reports on Industrial Misconduct, 1950-1957 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Court Cases - 1947, 1950-1951, 1947-1951 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Court Cases and Material on Disqualification - 1945-1952 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- NYS Supreme Court Appeals Court Brief and Record on Appeal, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Letters, Supporting Statements, Material on Disqualification (Misc.), 1945-1947 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- NYS Dept. of Labor Appeals Court Case, Brief, and Record on Appeal, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Memorandum of Conference with Lazare Teper of ILGWU Wednesday afternoon, December 20, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Historical and Organizational Background Material of Unemployment Insurance Programs August, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Mr. Alfred L. Green Nathan Morrison Draft of Statement on Unemployment Insurance Program Oct 27, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Materials on Seasonality (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Memorandum on the Proposals for Amendments of the New York Unemployment Insurance Law Submitted to the Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Advisory Council to the New York State Employment Service Expansion of the New York State Employment Service Feb 19, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Recommendations to the New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance, For Constructive Changes in New York's Unemployment Insurance Law, on behalf of organizations representing employers, farmers, and the public (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Farm Recruiting Program (Box 9, Folder 8)
- curtailment in the division's staffing program Aug 28, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- bi-weekly reports of the governor (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Notes on Visit to Manhattan Needle Trades Office 225 W. 34th Street, New York City April 22, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Suggested Formula for the application of penalties provided by Section 507a of the Unemployment Insurance Law (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Excerpts from Minutes of Planning Conference held in Spectacular, New York May 10 -13, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Stenographic Transcript Committee on Prevailing Wages May 9, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Unemployment Compensation Program Letter No. 58 April 8, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Inter-Office Memorandum May 8, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Liaison - UI and ES (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Statement to Ways and Means Committee of House of Representatives in Opposition to HR 6559 by Herman Gray (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Summary of Statement Made by Herman A Gray Chairman New York Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Contribution Rates: Merit Rating vs Flat Cut (Box 9, Folder 20)
- State by Herman Gray chairman of the Unemployment Insurance State Advisory Council March 6, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Summary of Address by Herman Gray on Partial Unemployment and Seasonality (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Conference of State Employment Security Attorneys and Appeal Bodies New York September 21, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- "Should the New York State unemployment Insurance Law Be Liberalized or Curtailed (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Statement by George J Mintzer Before the Joint Legislative Committee on Unemployment Insurance Thursday Nov 17, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Max Kaplan and Jacob Kaplan et al. to Review Order No. 3, dated October 30, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- To: HON. Frieda S Miller Industrial commissioner From: Mr. William J. Picard, Chairman Board of Standards and Appeals (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Directory Order Number 7 Governing Minimum Wage Standards in the Retail Trade Industry (Box 9, Folder 28)
- A.W.A. Pharmacy Inc. et al Case No. 1545-40 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- F. W. Woolworth Co. Review the Validity, Reasonableness, Legality and Constitutionality of directory Order No. 5 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Hon William J Picard Chairman Board of Standards and Appeals (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Frank E Allen doing Business under the assumed names of Home Dairy company 183 W Dominick St. Rome, NY Home Dairy Co. W Bridge St. Oswego, etc. (Box 9, Folder 32)
- In the Matter of the Petition of M. H. Fishman Co. (Box 9, Folder 33)
- In the Matter of the Petition of Waldorf System, Inc. Case No. 669-40 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Petition - Standard 5 and 10 cent Stores, Inc. Case No. 1140-40 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Petition - Ame Stores, Inc. et al., with place of business in the State of New York promulgated under Article 19 of the labor law (Box 9, Folder 36)